Shreyas S Sreedhar

Computer Science and Engineering Graduate

shreyas-sreedhar.com linkedin.com/in/shreyas-sreedhar shreyas.sreedhar@gmail.com

I'm a Senior Year Computer Science Engineering student at Jyothy IT, exploring interaction, data, augmented reality and virtual reality to solve problems by merging my analytical and creative halves to make meaningful products and experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Intern • Centre for eGovernance, Govt. of Karnataka April 2021 - June 2021

- » Worked with the team in Redesigning the Website by User interviews, Prototyping and user-tested Mahiti Kanaja, a Public Information Portal of the government of Karnataka.
- » Performed data-driven research on a small group to help understand the users and standardize visual design across the site and prototype new interactions and UI components.

Front-end Developer Intern • JyothyMediaWorks

May 2020 - July 2020

- » Created wire-frames, user flow diagrams and low fidelity prototypes and the Website User interfaces of JMW and JyothylCM.
- » Developed the Ul using HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap Framework.

Graphic Design Intern • Jyothy Institute of Technology

May 2018 - July 2020

- » Directed a team of 4 creating JIT's written and visual marketing strategy to strengthen our presence as the premier research and entrepreneurial based engineering college in Karnataka.
- » Defined college's brand guidelines and Bolstered brand's digital presence on social media.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Core Team — Pranathi — InterCollegiate Fest

Strategized, Organized, Hosted over 8 events in total from 2018-2020. Managed over 250 volunteers per event.

2nd Runners-up — 24Hours Gameathon 3.0

Designed a 3D game under 24 hours with a team of 4 using Blender, Unity and C#.

CERTIFICATIONS

Visual Elements of Ul Design — California Institute of the Arts

Data Science Orientation — Coursera

Al for Everyone — DeepLearning.Al

User Experience Design Essentials – Udemy

EDUCATION

B.E in Computer Science & Engineering

Jyothy Institute of Technology, Bangalore

August 2017 - August 2021 (Expected)

Aggregate: 6.98 CGPA (7th Semester)

Coursework: Data Structures, Design Analysis Of Algorithms, DBMS, Python, UI Design, BigData Analytics, Operating Systems, Machine

Learning, Networking, Internet of Things

PROJECTS

WIAS — Wildlife Intelligence and Automated Security

(Work in progress — Bachelor of Engineering Thesis)

Tech: Python, AWS, PyQT5, Open CV, Raspberry Pi, Blender.

Pranathi Fest Registration Management System

Intuitive Participant Admission Dashboard for college fests to make the registration process of college fests easier.

Tech: Figma, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JS and PHP.

Bike Showroom Database Management System

Web App that helps the admin to organize the data of the showroom with Joins, Triggers, Views and Stored Procedures.

Tech: MySQL, HTML, CSS, JS and PHP.

Minesweeper Game using OpenGL and C++

Basic minesweeper game using C++ and OpenGL.

SKILLS

| Languages | Tools | Design |
|------------|------------------|-------------------|
| HTML | MS Office | Wireframing |
| CSS | Azure (Familiar) | Rapid Protyping |
| JavaScript | AWS(Familiar) | Design Systems |
| Python | SparkAR | Value Proposition |
| PHP | Blender | Product Dev. |
| SQL | Figma | Affinity Diagrams |
| | Photoshop | AR / VR — 3D |